[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "3x4=?",
    "optionA": "12",
    "optionB": "45",
    "optionC": "10",
    "answer": "12"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "12x7=?",
    "optionA": "90",
    "optionB": "48",
    "optionC": "84",
    "answer": "84"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "36 divided by 4=?",
    "optionA": "12",
    "optionB": "9",
    "optionC": "7",
    "answer": "9"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "100 divided by 25=?",
    "optionA": "4",
    "optionB": "5",
    "optionC": "6",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "12+12=?",
    "optionA": "24",
    "optionB": "34",
    "optionC": "44",
    "answer": "24"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "12+24=?",
    "optionA": "12",
    "optionB": "24",
    "optionC": "36",
    "answer": "36"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "12-8=?",
    "optionA": "3",
    "optionB": "4",
    "optionC": "5",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "15x5=?",
    "optionA": "65",
    "optionB": "75",
    "optionC": "85",
    "answer": "75"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "36 divided by 12=?",
    "optionA": "3",
    "optionB": "4",
    "optionC": "5",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "56 divided by 4=?",
    "optionA": "12",
    "optionB": "13",
    "optionC": "14",
    "answer": "14"
  }
]
